Guide to the Northup & O'Brien Architectural Records
Northup & O'Brien Architectural Records
- Drawings, 1917-1980
  - Millingport School - Gymnasium, 1948 (Flatfolder 463)
  - Mineral Springs School - Addition, 1950 (Flatfolder 303)
  - Mineral Springs School - Alterations and Additions, 1924 (Flatfolder 387)
  - Mineral Springs School #2 - Alterations and Additions, 1950 (Flatfolder 69)
  - Mineral Springs School Gym, Addition, 1940 (Flatfolder 293)
  - Montague, P. N. - Residence, 1921 (Flatfolder 109)
  - Montaldos - New Entrance, 1973 (Flatfolder 404)
  - Monterey Transportation Company, 1976 (Flatfolder 557)
  - Moore, Baxter - Residence, 1926 (Flatfolder 115)
  - Moravian Chapel, 1925 (Flatfolder 578)
  - Moravian Chapel at Southside, 1928 (Flatfolder 147)
    Lincoln County, N.C.
  - Moravian Housing Corporation, 1972 (Flatfolder 230)
  - Morehead City School, 1950 (Flatfolder 565)
  - Mother and Daughter Store, 1945 (Flatfolder 302)
  - Mt. Airy High School, 1916 (Flatfolder 548)
  - Mt. Tabor Elementary School, 1957 (Flatfolder 518)
  - Mt. Tabor Methodist Church, 1947 (Flatfolder 317)
  - Mt. Ulla School, 1936 (Flatfolder 572)
  - NCNB Building, 1971 (Flatfolder 261)
  - NCNB Building, 1971 (Flatfolder 495)
  - NCNB Parking Deck, 1972 (Flatfolder 496)
  - NCNB Plaza, 1971 (Flatfolder 9)
  - NCNB Plaza, 1972 (Flatfolder 11)
  - NCNB Plaza, 1973 (Flatfolder 10)
  - NCNB Plaza, 1973 (Flatfolder 12)
  - NCNB Plaza, 1975 (Flatfolder 62)
  - NCNB Plaza, 1971 (Flatfolder 80)
  - NCNB Plaza (Flatfolder 239)
  - NCNB Plaza, 1917 (Flatfolder 511)
  - NCNB Topographic Map and Site Development, 1969 (Flatfolder 375)
  - New London School, 1936 (Flatfolder 61)
  - New Market School, 1936 (Flatfolder 396)
  - New North School, 1954 (Flatfolder 344)
  - New Woodrow Wilson School Building, 1936 (Flatfolder 424)
  - New Woodrow Wilson School Building - Addition and Alteration, 1936 (Flatfolder 425)
  - Norfleet, C. M. - Residence, 1923 (Flatfolder 132)
  - Norfleet, George S. - Residence, 1926 (Flatfolder 100)
  - Norfleet, J. K. - Residence, 1927 (Flatfolder 37)
  - Norman Stockton Inc. Renovation, 1973 (Flatfolder 406)
  - North Carolina Baptist Hospital - Addition and Alterations, 1943 (Flatfolder 305)
  - North Carolina Baptist Hospital - Nurses Home - Alterations and Additions, 1944 (Flatfolder 312)
  - North Carolina Baptist Hospital - Student Nurses Home, 1943 (Flatfolder 21)
  - North Carolina State University - Agriculture Laboratory, 1945 (Flatfolder 313)
  - North Carolina State University - Armory, 1949 (Flatfolder 59)
  - North Carolina State University - Bell Tower on Chemistry Building, 1943 (Flatfolder 415)
  - North Carolina State University - D. H. Hill Library, 1951 (Flatfolder 332)
  - North Carolina State University - Dormitories, 1946 (Flatfolder 314)
  - North Carolina State University - General Engineering Laboratory Building (Flatfolder 513)
  - North Carolina State University - General Engineering Lab Building, 1948 (Flatfolder 325)
  - North Carolina State University - General Engineering Lab Building, 1948 (Flatfolder 513)
  - North Carolina State University - Horticultural Laboratory, 1947 (Flatfolder 468)
  - North Carolina State University - Leazer Dining Hall - Alterations and Addition, 1947 (Flatfolder 319)
  - North Carolina State University - Library, 1951 (Flatfolder 265)
  - North Carolina State University - Mechanical Engineering Building, 1949 (Flatfolder 328)
  - North Carolina State University - Recreation and Dining Hall (Flatfolder 199)
  - North Durham School, 1929 (Flatfolder 163)
  - North Forsyth High School - Addition, 1965 (Flatfolder 393)
  - North Forsyth High School - Addition, 1965 (Flatfolder 525)
  - North Main Street School - Alterations and Additions, 1930 (Flatfolder 182)
  - North Main Street School - Alterations and Additions - Salisbury, 1935 (Flatfolder 222)
  - North Senior High School, 1962 (Flatfolder 63)
  - North Winston Salem Grade School, 1922 (Flatfolder 386)
  - Northup, W. C. - Tenament House, 1926 (Flatfolder 123)
  - Northwest High School - Addition, 1960 (Flatfolder 544)
  - Northwest High School - Cafeteria - Addition, 1960 (Flatfolder 350)
  - Norwood Colored School Building, 1936 (Flatfolder 282)
  - Norwood School Gymnasium, 1936 (Flatfolder 58)
  - Notes and sketches - unidentified, 1972 (Flatfolder 561)
  - O'Brien, L. A. - Residence, 1920 (Flatfolder 556)
  - Oak Ridge Consolidated School, 1923 (Flatfolder 360)
  - Oakboro School, 1936 (Flatfolder 79)
  - Old Richmond School - Gym, 1939 (Flatfolder 203)
  - Oldtown Consolidated School, 1924 (Flatfolder 358)
  - Oldtown Consolidated School - Addition, 1934 (Flatfolder 190)
  - Owen, L. F. - Residence and Garage, 1929 (Flatfolder 162)
  - Owen, L. F. - Cottage, 1925 (Flatfolder 435)
  - Paisley Jr. and Sr. High School - athletic field lighting, 19?? (Flatfolder 562)
  - Parking Deck - S. Salisbury Street, 1958 (Flatfolder 489)
  - Paschal, W. J. - Residence, 1935 (Flatfolder 271)
  - Paterson Group School Building, 1935 (Flatfolder 278)
  - Patten Building - Renovation, 1977 (Flatfolder 74)
  - Philadelphia School, 1928 (Flatfolder 441)
  - Philadelphia School - Auditorium - Addition, 1940 (Flatfolder 452)
  - Piedmont Aviation Reservation Center, 1969 (Flatfolder 394)
  - Piedmont Motor Company Garage, 1925 (Flatfolder 105)
  - Pilot Real Estate Company - Stores, 1927 (Flatfolder 135)
  - Plumly, Bess Gray - Residence, 1924 (Flatfolder 104)
  - Plumly, Charles E., Mrs. - Residence, 1913 (Flatfolder 119)
  - Professional Building - Annex, 1960 (Flatfolder 486)
  - Providence School, 1920 (Flatfolder 547)
  - Public Market, 1923 (Flatfolder 383)
  - R. J. Reynolds Tobacco Company - Pilot Plant, 1956 (Flatfolder 477)
  - R. J. Reynolds Tobacco Company - Research Laboratory Building - Addition, 1956 (Flatfolder 476)
  - R. J. Reynolds Tobacco Company Research Laboratory Building, 1956 (Flatfolder 50)
  - Rabb, S. W. - Residence, 1925 (Flatfolder 430)
  - Ramseur School - Alterations and Additions, 1935 (Flatfolder 276)
  - Randleman School - Alterations and Additions, 1926 (Flatfolder 227)
  - Randolph County Schools, 1936 (Flatfolder 40)
  - Reidsville Colored Grade School, 1920 (Flatfolder 211)
    Reidsville, Rockingham County, N.C.
  - Reidsville Colored Grade School, 1923 (Flatfolder 212)
  - Reidsville High School, 1920 (Flatfolder 485)
  - Reynolda House Costume Museum, 1972 (Flatfolder 232)
  - Reynolda Manor Branch Library, 1963 (Flatfolder 219)
  - Reynolda Polo Club - Clubhouse, 1926 (Flatfolder 124)
  - Reynolds Estate - Superintendent House, c.1926 (Flatfolder 129)
  - Reynolds Memorial Park - Old Church, 1954 (Flatfolder 474)
  - Reynolds Park Clubhouse, 1939 (Flatfolder 461)
  - Reynolds Park Gymnasium, 1939 (Flatfolder 413)
  - Reynolds, R. J. - Cottage, 1913 (Flatfolder 101)
  - Reynolds, R. J. - Gardener's Cottage, n.d. (Flatfolder 96)
  - Reynolds, R. J. - House, 1915 (Flatfolder 258)
    Forsyth County, N.C. This folder contains blueprints by Wiley Whitaker Contractors. It does NOT contain drawings by Northup O'Brien.
  - Reynolds, R. J. - Residence (Merry Acres), 1939 (Flatfolder 201)
  - Reynolds, R. J. Estate - Cottage, 1913 (Flatfolder 126)
  - Reynolds, R. J., Jr.- Girard Trust Building (Flatfolder 126)
    Sketch by Thomas W. Sears, Landscape Architect, Philadephia, PA.
  - Reynolds, W. N., Mrs. - Heating Stores, 1929 (Flatfolder 164)
  - Reynolds, W. N. - Residence -Tanglewood - Addition and Alterations (Flatfolder 145)
  - Richfield School - Alteration and Addition, 1936 (Flatfolder 419)
  - Richmond and Vienna Schools, 1927 (Flatfolder 210)
  - Ridgecrest School, 1936 (Flatfolder 422)
  - Ridgecrest School Gymnasium, 1948 (Flatfolder 469)
  - R. J. Reynolds Tobacco Company Research Laboratory Building, 1951 (Flatfolder 345)
  - Road Engineering drawings - various projects - unidentified, 1945-1972 (Flatfolder 558)
  - Roanoke Rapids School Building, 1924 (Flatfolder 204)
    Roanoke Rapids, Halifax County, N.C.
  - Rockford Grade School - Alterations and Additions, 1930 (Flatfolder 176)
  - Rogers, Joseph, 1922 (Flatfolder 550)
  - Rousseau, J. P. - Residence, 1928 (Flatfolder 428)
  - Rowan County Schools - various plans, 1935 (Flatfolder 73)
  - Rural Hall Consolidated School, 1923 (Flatfolder 364)
  - Saint Mary's School Dormitory, 1928 (Flatfolder 152)
  - Salem Cemetery Mausoleum, 1963 (Flatfolder 221)
  - Salem College - Addition To Gymnasium, 1958 (Flatfolder 488)
  - Salem College - Master Plan, 1970 (Flatfolder 403)
  - Salem Home, 1925 (Flatfolder 110)
  - Salem Steel Company - Office Building, 1965 (Flatfolder 218)
  - Salem Steel Company - Office Building, 1938 (Flatfolder 299)
  - Salisbury Colored Grade School, 1922 (Flatfolder 200)
  - School for Handicapped Children, 1957 (Flatfolder 523)
  - Seagrove Consolidated School, 1934 (Flatfolder 189)
  - Seagrove Consolidated School, 1926 (Flatfolder 498)
  - Sedge Garden Elementary School - Replacement, 1978 (Flatfolder 87)
  - Sedge Garden Elementary School - Replacement, 1978 (Flatfolder 88)
  - Sedge Garden School, 1925 (Flatfolder 223)
  - Sedge Garden School - Addition, 1937 (Flatfolder 279)
  - Sedge Garden School - Gym, 1938 (Flatfolder 455)
  - Shaffner, Fries - Residence, 1937 (Flatfolder 571)
  - Shaffner, Henry F. - Residence, 1907 (Flatfolder 118)
  - Sheppard, Kent - Residence, ca. 1930 (Flatfolder 436)
  - Shore Factory Building, 1935 (Flatfolder 553)
  - Siewers, W. L. - Residence, 1915 (Flatfolder 128)
  - Slane, W. H. - Residence, 1929 (Flatfolder 34)
  - Smith Grove Consolidated School, 1927 (Flatfolder 432)
  - Smith Grove Consolidated School, 1923 (Flatfolder 384)
  - Smith, J. R. - Apartment Building, 1935 (Flatfolder 262)
  - Smith, Raymond - Cottage, 1933 (Flatfolder 66)
  - Solid Waste Disposal Facility, 1972 (Flatfolder 231)
  - South Fork Consolidated School, 1926 (Flatfolder 208)
  - South Junior High School, 1929 (Flatfolder 159)
  - Southern Furniture Company, 1968 (Flatfolder 408)
  - Southside Moravian Church, 1920 (Flatfolder 370)
  - Spach, Jule - Residence, 1928 (Flatfolder 156)
  - Sprunt, W. H. - Residence, 1928 (Flatfolder 158)
  - St. Anne's Episcopal Church, 1966 (Flatfolder 409)
  - St. Joseph Church - Parish House, 1928 (Flatfolder 153)
  - St. Paul's Lutheran Church, 1927 (Flatfolder 141)
  - St. Paul's Lutheran Church, 1928 (Flatfolder 168)
  - Staley School - Alterations and Additions, 1935 (Flatfolder 569)
  - Stanly County School - Various, 1936 (Flatfolder 423)
  - Stanly County Jail, 1936 (Flatfolder 56)
  - Stanly County Sewage Treatment Plant, 1936 (Flatfolder 563)
  - State Hospital - Alterations, 1945 (Flatfolder 473)
  - State Hospital - Broughton Building, 1949 (Flatfolder 465)
  - State Hospital - Disturbed Men's Building, 1949 (Flatfolder 51)
  - State Hospital - Nurses Home - Alterations and Additions, 1944 (Flatfolder 472)
  - State Hospital of North Carolina - Building for Epileptic Children, 1946 (Flatfolder 466)
  - State Hospital of North Carolina - Clark Building - Renovation, 1948 (Flatfolder 480)
  - State Office Building, 1937 (Flatfolder 24)
    Wake County, N.C. This project is probably the State of North Carolina Education Building.
  - State Office Building, 1937 (Flatfolder 446)
  - Stockton, Richard - Residence - Addition, 1973 (Flatfolder 247)
  - Stokes County Consolidated Schools - Addition, 1930 (Flatfolder 173)
  - Stokes County Consolidated School, 1922 (Flatfolder 362)
  - Stokes County Schools (Flatfolder 292)
  - Stokesdale Consolidated School, 1923 (Flatfolder 373)
    Stokesdale, Guilford County, N.C.
  - Tabernacle School, 1936 (Flatfolder 567)
  - Tara Condominiums, 1979 (Flatfolder 493)
  - Taylor, Barrett - Residence, 19?? (Flatfolder 120)
  - Taylor, Harry - Residence and Alterations, 1916-1928 (Flatfolder 154)
  - Terry, R. B. Residence - Alterations and Additions, 1941 (Flatfolder 47)
  - Textbook and Archives Building, 1951 (Flatfolder 533)
  - Thomas, W. R. - Residence, 1928 (Flatfolder 427)
  - Thruway Shop Center - John Simmons Addition, 1970 (Flatfolder 7)
  - Thruway Shop Center - Roses Stores, 1964 (Flatfolder 1)
  - Thruway Shop Center - Various Stores, 1965 (Flatfolder 509)
  - Thruway Shop Center - Wilson - Pleasants, 1965 (Flatfolder 2)
  - Thruway Shop Center - Winn-Dixie, 1964 (Flatfolder 499)
  - Thruway Shop Center - Winn-Dixie, 1970 (Flatfolder 8)
  - Thruway Shopping Center - Food Fair - Addition, 1971 (Flatfolder 236)
  - Thruway Shopping Center - Site Work, 1964 (Flatfolder 391)
  - Thruway Shopping Center - Stores, 1967 (Flatfolder 4)
  - Thruway Shopping Center - Thalhimers - Addition, 1968 (Flatfolder 5)
  - Thruway Shopping Center - Woolworth Store, 1962 (Flatfolder 354)
  - Thruway Shopping Center Store, 1961 (Flatfolder 353)
  - Tom Cash School, 1955 (Flatfolder 535)
  - Trinity Moravian Choir, 1966 (Flatfolder 410)
  - Trinity Moravian Church - Addition, 1973 (Flatfolder 259)
  - Trinity Moravian Church - Additions and Alteration (Flatfolder 416)
  - Trinity Moravian Church - Douglas Rights Chapel, 1959 (Flatfolder 349)
  - Trinity School, 1924 (Flatfolder 215)
  - Tryon Palace Restoration, 1954 (Flatfolder 475)
    Craven County, N.C.
  - Union Cross School, 1928 (Flatfolder 170)
  - University of North Carolina at Greensboro - Aycock Auditorium Alteration, 1976 (Flatfolder 78)
  - University of North Carolina at Greensboro - Nursery School, 1953 (Flatfolder 335)
  - University of North Carolina at Greensboro - Aycock Auditorium (Flatfolder 228)
  - University of North Carolina at Greensboro - Aycock Auditorium (Flatfolder 229)
  - University of North Carolina at Greensboro - Laundry Building, 1947 (Flatfolder 321)
  - University of North Carolina at Greensboro - Women's College - Student Union Building, 1950 (Flatfolder 65)
  - University of North Carolina at Greensboro - Womens College - Dining Hall Alteration, 1948 (Flatfolder 514)
  - University of North Carolina at Greensboro - Womens College - Dormitory, 1948 (Flatfolder 70)
  - University of North Carolina at Greensboro - Womens College - Home Economics Building, 1949 (Flatfolder 327)
  - University of North Carolina at Greensboro - Womens College - Infirmary, 1951 (Flatfolder 482)
  - University of North Carolina at Greensboro - Womens College - Library, 1948 (Flatfolder 324)
  - University of North Carolina at Greensboro - Womens College - Shop and Maintenance Building, 1952 (Flatfolder 516)
  - Upper Morgan Township School Building, 1935 (Flatfolder 398)
  - Vance Knitting Company - Addition, 1935 (Flatfolder 273)
  - Vass, Harry - Residence, 1928 (Flatfolder 442)
  - Veterans of Foreign Wars - Clubhouse, 1931 (Flatfolder 570)
  - Vogler, F. E. - Residence, 1924 (Flatfolder 143)
  - Vulcan Materials Company - Office Building, 1969 (Flatfolder 555)
  - W. A. Whitaker School - Classroom Addition, 1956 (Flatfolder 339)
  - Wachovia Bank and Office Building, 1924 (Flatfolder 93)
    Salisbury, Rowan County, N.C.
  - Walkertown Jr. High School - Addition, 1973 (Flatfolder 248)
  - Walkertown School, 1924 (Flatfolder 382)
  - Walkertown School - Alterations and Additions, 1928 (Flatfolder 149)
  - Walkertown School - Gym, 1936 (Flatfolder 504)
  - Wall, C. C. - Residence, 1922 (Flatfolder 39)
  - War Memorial Auditorium, 1975 (Flatfolder 243)
  - Ward, Robert - Residence, 1975 (Flatfolder 81)
  - Washington Mills School Building, 1924 (Flatfolder 368)
  - Watts, R. L. - Residence, 1923 (Flatfolder 94)
  - Waughtown Grade School, 1921 (Flatfolder 363)
  - Waughtown Grade School - Addition, 1929 (Flatfolder 365)
  - Wesley B. Speas Elementary School - Addition, 1958 (Flatfolder 347)
  - West End School - Alterations and Additions (Flatfolder 497)
  - West Highlands Presbyterian Church, 1922 (Flatfolder 106)
  - West Salem Grade School, 1914 (Flatfolder 225)
  - West Ward Grade School, 1922 (Flatfolder 53)
  - West Ward Grade School, 1921 (Flatfolder 400)
  - West Yadkin School, 1935 (Flatfolder 448)
  - Whitaker, G. B. - Residence, 1924 (Flatfolder 108)
  - Whitaker, John C. - Boat House, 1934 (Flatfolder 185)
  - Whitaker, John C. - Greenhouse, 1934 (Flatfolder 186)
  - Whitaker, John C. - Residence, 1932 (Flatfolder 194)
  - White Rock School, 1954 (Flatfolder 342)
  - White, G. C. - Store Building, 1928 (Flatfolder 83)
  - Wiley Jr. High School - Conversion, 1958 (Flatfolder 16)
  - Willis, M. H.- Residence, 1927 (Flatfolder 288)
  - Wilson, T. Henry - Residence, 1939 (Flatfolder 460)
  - Wilson, P. T. - Residence, 1927 (Flatfolder 137)
  - Wilson, Thomas Residence, 1945 (Flatfolder 531)
  - Winston Salem Airport Terminal Building, 1937 (Flatfolder 291)
  - Winston Salem Fire Station, 1922 (Flatfolder 92)
  - Winston Salem Housing Authority - Cleveland Homes Daycare, 1969 (Flatfolder 401)
  - Winston Salem Housing Authority - Central Office Building Addition, 1961 (Flatfolder 352)
  - Winston Salem Housing Authority - Haws Sunrise Crystal Towers, 1979 (Flatfolder 86)
  - Winston Salem Housing Authority - Piedmont Park, 1951 (Flatfolder 334)
  - Winston Salem Public Library, 1952 (Flatfolder 198)
  - Winston Salem Savings and Loan, 1974 (Flatfolder 519)
  - Winston Salem Savings and Loan, 1974 (Flatfolder 532)
  - Winston Salem State College - Administration Building Alterations, 1938 (Flatfolder 522)
  - Winston Salem State College - Bickett Hall - Renovations, 1968 (Flatfolder 412)
  - Winston Salem State College - Science Building Alterations and Additions, 1967 (Flatfolder 411)
  - Winston Salem State Teachers College - Science Building, 1938 (Flatfolder 458)
  - Winston Salem State University -Boy's Dorm (Bickett) - Alterations and Additions, 1950 (Flatfolder 549)
  - Winston Salem State University - Health and Physical Education Building - Alterations and Additions, 1974 (Flatfolder 55)
  - Winston Salem Teachers College - Atkins Hall Addition, 1948 (Flatfolder 534)
  - Winston Salem Teachers College - Library and Administration Building, 1938 (Flatfolder 297)
  - Winston Salem Teachers College - Library and Administration Building, 1938-1939 (Flatfolder 298)
  - Winston Salem University - Health and Physical Education Building - Renovation and Addition, 1974 (Flatfolder 505)
  - Woman's College at University of North Carolina at Greensboro - Homemaking Cottage, 1947 (Flatfolder 320)
  - Woman's College University of North Carolina at Greensboro - Luncheonette Building, 1947 (Flatfolder 540)
  - Womble, Carlyle, Sandridge and Rice Law Offices, 1965 (Flatfolder 407)
  - Womble, W.F. Residence, 1927 (Flatfolder 138)
  - Woodland Ave. Colored School, 1914 (Flatfolder 361)
  - Woodland School Addition, 1954 (Flatfolder 17)
  - Woodrow Wilson School, 1936 (Flatfolder 574)
  - Woods, Jr., R. H. - Residence, 1929 (Flatfolder 161)
- Specifications, 31 linear feet
  This series consists of volumes containing specifications for architectural projects. Included are technical specifications and contracts, as well as correspondence and other material relating to specific jobs. Some volumes relate to specific aspects of jobs, such as plumbing and heating. Thus, some material for a particular job is located in more than one volume. This series is arranged by commission (job) number.
  - Farm House for Mr. R. D. Shore, Winston-Salem, N.C., undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Bethlehem Home for Centenary West End Church, Wiston-Salem, N.C., undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Residence and Garage for Mr. W. F. Brown, Lexington, N.C., undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Mr. C. T. Leinbach, Addition to House, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - House for J. Barton Benson, Rydal, PA, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Residence for Mrs. P. A. Gorrell, Winston Salem, N.C., 1926 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Boys' Dormitory for Methodist Children's Home, Winston-Salem, N.C., undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Ardmore Moravian Church, Ardmore (Winston-Salem), N.C., undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Residence and Garage for Mr. Ham Horton, Winston-Salem, N.C., undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Alterations to Stone Building for H. R. Stanbuck, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Storage Building and Dairy Farm Building for Mr. R. E. Lasater, Winston-Salem, N.C., undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Sunday School Building for First Presbyterian Church, Winston-Salem, N.C., undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Lee Memorial Presbyterian Church, Winston-Salem, N.C., undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Mill Building for Mr. R. E. Lasater, Winston-Salem, N.C., undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Residence for Mr. A. L. Butner, Winston-Salem, N.C., undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Residence, Garage, and Gardener's Cottage for Mr. John C. Whitaker, Winston-Salem, N.C., undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Residence and Garage for Mr. C. L. Creech, Winston-Salem, N.C., undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Residence and Garage for Mr. C. C. Garrett, Winston-Salem, N.C., undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Residence and Garage for Mr. Hargrove Bellamy, Wilmington, N.C., 192? (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Cottage for Mr. Raymond Smith, Roaring Gap, N.C., 1933 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Garage and Servants Quarters for W. H. Hendren, Winston-Salem, N.C., 1934 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Apartment Building for Mr. J. R. Thomas, Winston-Salem, N.C., undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Alterations to Residence for Mr. R. T. Amos, High Point, N.C., undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Seagrove Consolidated School, Seagrove, N.C., 1926 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Alterations and Additions to Old Town Consolidated School, Old Town, N.C., 1934 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Alterations and Additions to Griffith Consolidated School, Winston-Salem, N.C., 1934 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Cottage for Mr. R. E. Caster, Roaring Gap, N.C., undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Cottage for Athletic Director, Children's Home, Winston-Salem, N.C., undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Residence and Garage for Mrs. Lindsey Holcomb, Mt. Airy, N.C., undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Alterations in a Business Block for Amos Realty, Reidsville, N.C., undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Heating and Plumbing at Stanly County Schools: Aquadate, Endy, Ridgecrest, and Millingsport, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Plumbing and Heating at Norwood Gymnasium, Norwood, N.C., 1936 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Plumbing and Heating at Kingville Colored School, Kingville (Albemarle), N.C., 1936 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Residence and Garage for Roy D. McKenzie, Winston-Salem, N.C., 1936 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Alterations to Clemmons School, Clemmons, N.C., 1936 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Heating and Plumbing for Girls Dormitory at Children's Home, Winston-Salem, N.C., undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Lawsonville School, Stokes County Schools, N.C., undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - White Rock School, Forsyth County, N.C. (no specs, just title sheet), undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - apl. Salem College (empty), undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Alterations and Additions to Heating Equipment for Asheboro Jail and Court House, Asheboro, N.C., 1936 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Plumbing and Heating Alterations at Residence of Mr. and Mrs. D. L. Drummond, Winston-Salem, N.C., 1936 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Hanes Barn (empty), undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Residence for Mr. John Dillard, Winston-Salem, N.C., 1936 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Residence for Dr. C. L. Cruse, Winston-Salem, N.C., 1936 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Office Building for Chatham Manufacturing Company, Winston-Salem, N.C., 1936 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - H. G. Hudson Residence Heating and Plumbing Spec., 1937 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Residence for Mr. Scott Fillman, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Garage County Home, Forsyth County Board of Commissioners (No Specs.), undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Fries Shaffner Residence (H & P), undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Dr. Edward Ashby Residence (H & P), undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - P. H. Hanes Knitting Company (No Specs), undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Dr. C. A. Blackburn Residence - P & H, undated (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Randolph County Extension Building, undated (Box 2, Folder 31)